BENEDICT N. KABOYOKA

P. O. Box 66675, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania

Phone: +255 759 160 978 E-mail: <u>kaboyokabenedict@gmail.com</u>

CURRICULUM VITAE

NAME: BENEDICT NSANGIJO KABOYOKA

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of birth: 11th July 1997

Gender: Male

Nationality: Tanzanian

PERSONAL PROFILE

Passionate and committed to giving back to the community using the knowledge, experience and skills gathered over the course of life. Extremely trustworthy and well organized with excellent attention to detail, striving for cultural diversity with strong desires, motivated to learn, grow and excel in new concepts

EDUCATION

EDUCATION DATE	INSTITUTION	QUALIFICATION/AWARDS
2017 -2020	University of Dar es Salaam	Bachelor of Science in
		Computer Science
2015-2017	Baobab Secondary School	Certificate for Secondary
		School Education (ACSSE)
2010-2014	Uru minor Seminary	Certificate of Secondary School
		Education (CSSE)

WORKING EXPERIENCE

1. January 2021 – Present Senjaro delivery company(Mobile developer).

- My responsibility at Senjaro was to modify the User Interface of the current application which is already on production by adding new feature according to the designs provided. Tech stack used were React Native, Native base and Firebase for data storage.
- Created a company dashboard website which was used to view orders made by users from mobile application. Technology used were Reactjs, Material UI and Axios for data fetching.
- Acte as a IT Technician were I helped with all technical problem at the office from computer troubleshooting and simple maintenance (Windows problem).

BENEDICT N. KABOYOKA

P. O. Box 66675, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania

Phone: +255 759 160 978 E-mail: kaboyokabenedict@gmail.com

CURRICULUM VITAE

2. June 2019 - August 2019 University of Dar es Salaam, UDSM. (UI/UX Designer Intern).

Working as intern UI/UX designer, my responsibilities include but not limited to;

- Collaborated in U/UX design of the department information management system using designing tools like Adobe XD and Figma.
- Participated in Front-End development of the system using Angular Framework.

3. June 2018 – August 2018 Index Labs Tanzania (Front End developer, Trainee)

- Conceived and built optimized landing pages in HTML and CSS.
- Learned Laravel, PHP framework.
- Learned database design and management.
- Learn how to use SQL to store, query, and manipulate data.

TRAINING, PROJECTS AND CONFERENCE ATTENDANCE

- 1. Participated in the Andela Learning Community program in 2018. I joined the Mobile web specialist track.
 - Learnt ReactJS fundamentals
 - Web designing and website development (HTML, CSS and Javascript)
- 2. Participated in Google Africa Developer Scholarship in 2019. This was 150 days to access learning material from prulasight.

PROJECT

1. Develop Mobile application for Village Community Banks (VICOBA)

Link to the project on GitHub

- Presented the project to the University as my Final Year Project
- The application was developed using React Native, Firebase, Hasura, Graphql and PostgreSQL database
- Project aims at managing and collection information of VICOBA group members
- Information includes daily contribution and their records.

2. Developed Mobile application for SENJARO

• OnDemand service app from Food delivery, Courier To HandyMan Services

Other projects are available on GitHub

Link to GitHub profile Benkabo

BENEDICT N. KABOYOKA

P. O. Box 66675, Dar es Salaam, Tanzania

Phone: +255 759 160 978 E-mail: kaboyokabenedict@gmail.com

CURRICULUM VITAE

SKILLS

- React JS (Novice)
- HTML and CSS
- JavaScript
- React Native (Novice)
- UI/UX designing
- Web designing and development

LANGUAGES

Swahili (Native)	English (Excellent)

I certify that the information in this CV is true and accurate to the best of my knowledge.